welcome back to this tutorial. So who is the target audience for this tutorial?
The target audience for this tutorial is not only for IT professionals but also for
those who want to become an IT professional or land IT skills. Are you working as
an IT hot desk engineer or an IT service desk engineer or IT system administrator?
Definitely, you're going to learn a lot from this tutorial. But if you just
want to improve your IT skills, learn new information on network and system
technology, definitely this training is for you. You don't need to have any
IT background or IT knowledge to be able to follow up on this tutorial. You don't
need to have some very very business skills on item system networking to be
able to understand and follow up on this training.